Welcome to ArtsFolio.
In this short tour, you’ll learn how to navigate your admin area,
understand the dashboard, preview your site, and find help.
After you sign in, first confirm that you’re working on the correct site.
Your site name appears in the admin sidebar.
This prevents edits from landing in the wrong studio.
The sidebar is your main map.
Dashboard returns to the overview.
Content holds About and Contact material.
Artworks, Portfolio Sections, Events, Messages, Sales,
Settings, and Help each lead to a focused workspace.
Think of the dashboard as your control room.
Use it to spot items needing attention,
jump to common tasks, and confirm normal activity.
The dashboard gives you the signal.
The detailed page gives you the tools.
Keep your public site close while you work.
Edit one area, save it, then inspect the public result,
especially on a phone.
The Onboarding page gathers your setup tools in one place.
Use the checklist, guided tour, function index,
and training resources.
Resetting onboarding progress does not delete your site content,
artwork, settings, users, messages, or sales.
Help is available from inside your site.
The function index explains what each admin page does,
when to use it, and what to check before saving.
Written guides can remain open in another tab while you work.
Change one group of settings at a time.
Save before leaving the page.
Read validation messages and inspect the relevant public page
on desktop and mobile.
Treat your admin area as private workspace.
Invite helpers through Users instead of sharing passwords,
and do not expose customer or visitor information.
The sidebar is your map, the dashboard is your control room,
and the public site is your proof.
Next: site identity, branding, and content.